temasekreview.com 2010-05-25

# THE TEMASEK REVIEW: Privacy Policy

**Our Commitment to Privacy**

Our Privacy Policy is designed to assist you in understanding how we collect, use and safeguard the personal data you provide to us and to assist you in making informed decisions when using the Temasek Review (TR) Web site and our products and services.

Our Privacy Policy may be amended from time to time. You should check our Privacy Policy regularly to ensure you are aware of our latest policies.  
**  
What Information Do We Collect?**

When you visit the TR Web site, we may collect two types of information from you: personal data you knowingly choose to disclose that is collected on an individual basis and the TR Web site user information collected on an aggregate basis as you and others browse the TR Web site.

**Credit Card Information**

If you choose to purchase products or services from us, you may need to give personal data and authorise us to obtain information from various credit services. For example, you may need to provide the following information:

•     Name  
•     E-mail address  
•     Identity reference  
•     Credit card number and expiry date  
•     Telephone or fax or pager number

In addition to providing the foregoing personal data to us, if you choose to correspond further with us through e-mail, we may retain the content of your e-mail messages together with your e-mail address and our responses. We provide the same protections for these electronic communications that we employ in the maintenance of information received by mail and telephone.

**SCMP Security Statement**

This web site is secured to protect your credit card number, name and other personal information from unauthorized access. All personal information is also encrypted for transmission over the Internet (using 128-bit SSL encryption).

**User Information**

**Cookies**

The TR Web site utilises Web server logs and will use a standard technology called “cookies” to recognize you and your access privileges on the TR Web site as well as to collect information about how the TR Web site is used. Information gathered by using cookies and Web server logs may include the date and time of visits, the pages viewed, time spent at the TR Web site, and the web sites you visited immediately before and after the TR Web site. This information is collected on an aggregate basis. None of this information is associated with you as an individual.

**IP Addresses**

Like all other servers in the world, we log IP addresses or the location of your computer on the Internet, for systems administration and troubleshooting purposes. We do not use IP address logs to track your session or your behaviour on the TR Web site.
